Hello, everybody out there.
Welcome you all to SPIRIT Club
Virtual Boxing Fitness.
My name is Kristian.
Thank you all for being here
today.
Along with me to give you all a
great boxing workout, we have
two amazing trainers who are
going to introduce themselves
to you all.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Marcella.
Very happy to be here with you.
I hope you guys enjoy the class.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Avery.
Thanks for joining us today.
Like Marcela said, I hope you
guys are ready for a great class.
Let's jump right into it,
Kristian.
All right, let's do it, Avery.
Let's do it, Marcela.
Let's go, everybody.
So we're going to kick our
class off with some warm up
exercises so we can get the
blood flowing, get our
body parts
ready for some action.
All right, so first thing we're
going to start with everybody,
we're just going to do some
side bends.
So let's spread those arms out
to the side, and then we're
going to lean left to right,
trying to reach those
fingertips as close to the
floor as we can.
Here we go.
Good job, everybody.
Looking good, Avery and Marcela.
Make sure you all are reaching
those fingertips a little bit
lower each time.
Good work, Avery.
Good job, Marcela.
10 seconds, everybody.
Keep it going.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Good job.
Next up, we're going to bring
our elbows up to our sides and
we're going to twist left to
right.
This is our torso twist.
We're going to open up our hips
and our midsections by twisting
side to side.
Here we go.
Good job, everybody.
Nice work, Avery.
Excellent, Marcela.
Keep it going, everybody.
All right, we're going to add
on to our twist with some
punches so twist and punch.
Twist and punch.
Everybody, let's go.
Good job.
We got 15 seconds.
Let's go faster.
Pick it up.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome, everybody.
All right, we're going to move
on to our arms next.
So we're going to wrap our arms
up around our upper bodies,
give ourselves a nice big
squeeze, and then we're going
to pull them apart, big and wide.
This is our SPIRIT fly.
Get our chest and shoulders
nice and ready.
All right.
Nice stretch, Avery, way to
open those arms up.
Awesome work, Marcela.
All right, everybody, 10
seconds.
Let's try to pull those arms
back further.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Nice, everybody.
Up next, we're going to do some
swings.
We're going to do some leg
swings and some arm swings.
So here's the leg swings.
If you want to do the arm
swings, you can follow along
with Avery.
There it is right there.
Getting those legs and arms up.
Getting a nice reach, everybody,
so let's get to it.
Good work, Marcela.
Good job, everyone.
Keep it going.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome.
All right, we're going to get
into a little bit of cardio so
we can get our heart rates up.
So what we're going to do next,
everybody, is some jump rope.
Let's get those invisible jump
ropes out.
Get a bounce going.
Let's move it.
Good job, everybody.
All right.
Nice, Avery.
Good job, Marcela.
All right, you all, we're
almost there.
We got 15 seconds.
Let's see if we can move it a
little faster.
Awesome.
We got 5,
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
All right, keep that bounce
going, everybody.
Up next we're going to run in
place.
So we're keeping our bounce
going, but we're going to pump
our arms to go along with it.
So we're just running in place.
If you have some space, you can
go side to side,
forward and back.
All right.
Nice arm swing, Avery, keep
those arms pumping.
All right.
Nice, Marcela.
Let's double time, everybody.
Faster, faster, faster.
All right, so up next, we're
going to do a little bit of
speedbag.
So we're going to keep the
bounce going, but we're going
to roll one hand over the other
as fast as we can, just like we
would if we're hitting the
speedbag.
Let's do it.
You can go up, down, side to
side,
just keep those hands rolling.
Good job, everybody.
10 seconds.
Look at those quick hands from
Avery.
Good job.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Excellent, everybody.
Good job, Marcela.
Good job, Avery.
All right, you all, we're going
to take ourselves a quick break.
While we're taking our break,
you all can get yourself set up
by having water, of course, so
you can stay hydrated.
Keep a chair nearby just so you
can rest up in between our
breaks.
And if you do have boxing
gloves, you can get those laced
up now.
And we're going to start in
about 30 seconds, everybody.
Good job with the warm up.
Hope you all are feeling fired
up and ready to go.
We're going to have some fun
today.
That was a great warm up.
Nice.
Yes, it was.
The music helped.
Yeah, definitely.
All right, Marcela, Avery, are
we ready to go?
Ready to go.
Ready.
Let's do it.
All right, you all, so here we
go.
First thing we're going to do,
everybody, we're going to start
it off with a little general
exercise so we can get a little
bit more warmed up, get our
body nice and fluid.
So we're going to start off
with some floor touches.
So we're going to reach those
hands up high, and then we're
reaching them down towards the
floor.
And even if you can't touch the
floor, just reach those
fingertips as close as you can
and try to get a little closer
each time.
So we're going up and down.
Let's do it.
Good work, Marcela.
Good job, Avery.
Awesome, everybody out there,
keep it going.
We've got 10 seconds.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome, everybody.
All right, we're going to
change gears now.
We're going into boxing mode.
So let's get those hands up.
The back hand is going to be
covering the face.
The front is going to cover the
body.
If you're doing this one
standing, you're going to have
a staggered stance.
One foot in front of the other.
And we're just going to get a
nice bounce going while we're
in our boxing stance.
All right, so let's do it.
Move around a little bit,
find your rhythm.
All right, there's Avery.
He's feeling it.
He's got those hands up.
He's ready for anything.
Marcela, same thing.
She's ready to go.
So let's do it, everybody,
first punch.
We're going to start off with
our right jab.
So we're just throwing a
straightforward punch and then
back into our stance with the
hands up.
So quick right jab.
And as you're throwing those
punches, make sure you lean
into them to get more power,
get better balance.
Let's see it, Marcela.
Nice.
Good job.
Way to step into those punches.
All right, let's switch it up
to the left jab, everybody.
Left jab.
Let's go.
All right, there's Avery with
those blazing flash jabs.
Good job.
Good work, everybody.
Let's bring the two together.
Now we're going right and left
jab back to back.
Good job, everybody.
Right and left.
All right.
We change it up in the other
direction.
We'll go left and right.
We'll go back and forth between
the two.
Leading with the left, leading
with the right.
Awesome, Marcela.
All right, everybody, we got 5,
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Nice work.
All right, we've got one more
thing before we move along.
We're going to take the floor
touch and the jabs and we're
going to put the two together
just so we can work on some
coordination, being able to
switch gears in an instant.
So we're going to touch our
toes, pop up, one, two jab.
Floor touch, quick, jab, jab.
Awesome, everybody.
Floor touch, pop up, jab, jab.
There you go, Avery.
Nice work.
All right, let's take it a step
further, everybody.
Floor touch, pop up, four jabs,
1, 2, 3, 4.
And a little bit more quickness
with those punches.
Let's go.
Good job, Marcela.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Way to go, everybody.
Great job.
Alright, we're gonna pass it
along to Avery.
He's going to lead us with the
next segment.
All right, Kristian, what we're
going to start off doing this
time around, we're going to
start off doing some shoulder
presses.
We're going to get about a good
30 seconds in of just pressing
up,
like raising the roof.
Let's get about 30 seconds in
of this, okay?
Just like that.
Great job.
There's Marcela.
Great job, Marcela.
Kristian raising the roof.
Already feeling the burn.
All right, we're about 15
seconds in.
Let's finish it out strong.
Let's pick it up a little bit.
All right, 5,
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
All right, great job.
With that, we're going to jump
right back into our boxing
stance.
This time around, we're going
to start off just throwing some
right hook punches, okay?
And remember, when you're
throwing this hook punch, you
want to follow through all the
way across the front of your
chest.
Great job, Kristian.
All right, we're going to
switch to our left,
just left hook punches only.
Great job, Marcela.
All right, let's get a few more
in and then we're going to put
them both together.
All right, let's put them both
together.
That's going to be a right and
a left.
Great job transitioning, guys.
Keep it up.
Great job, everyone.
Keep going.
Don't stop.
Don't think about it.
Just keep throwing those
punches.
All right, let's get ready to
put four of them together,
everyone.
So it's going to be
1,
2,
3,
4.
Four quick hook punches.
Great job, Marcela.
All right, let's go for 30
seconds, let's finish it out.
And remember, you want to reset
after you throw your punches.
Hands back up, four punches.
Hands up, four punches.
All right, we got 10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
All right, great job, everyone.
Before I pass it along to
Marcella, we're going to jump
right back into our shoulder
presses, and we're going to
incorporate hook punches.
Let's say five chest presses,
and then we're going to throw
four hook punches.
Okay?
So 1,
2,
3,
4,
5----------
5----------
1,
2,
3,
4.
All right?
Great job, everyone.
Keep it up.
Nice combination, Avery.
Feeling it.
All right, we got 10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome job, everyone.
Now I'll pass it along to
Marcella and see what she has up
next.
All right.
Thank you, Avery.
Okay, our next target movement
is going to be our jumping jacks.
So I'm going to be doing the
standing version, which is I'm
going to tap to the side, bring
my arms overhead
right in the middle.
If you're doing the advanced
version, you can follow along
with Kristian.
Nice.
Nice work.
Good job, Avery.
Keep it going for 20 seconds.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome.
All right,
we're going to do our uppercut,
so we're going to start with
the right uppercut.
You're going to lean on the leg
that is in front of you and
bring that uppercut all the way
through your hips.
All the way through.
So let's do it.
Right uppercuts.
Just like that.
Very good.
Good, Avery.
Okay, let's do our left
uppercuts.
Left.
Good job, everyone.
Keep it going.
All right, let's do them
together.
Right, left, right, left
uppercuts.
All right, let's go.
Right and left, good job.
Good work, Avery.
Excellent.
Keep it going for 20 more
seconds.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
All right, keep moving, guys.
We are going to add the jumping
jack to our punches, so we're
going to do two jumping jacks,
two uppercuts.
So let's try this.
That's 1,
2,
uppercut, uppercut.
1,
2,
uppercut, uppercut.
There you go.
Uppercut,
jumping jacks.
Nice.
Good job, Kristian.
Awesome, Avery.
Nice work.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Great job.
All right.
Amazing stuff, Marcela.
Good job, Avery.
Good job, everybody.
Awesome work.
That was not easy combining
those exercises with the punches.
Let's go get some water.
Good job, everyone.
Oh, man, that was tough.
Coordination.
Was it easy?
Not at all.
But we did it, Marcela and
Avery, we made it through
everybody, so
we win.
But there's more to come,
everybody, so good job.
That was our first round.
Before we officially take a
break, we're going to pick
ourselves back up and get ready
for our challenge, where we're
going to do 1 minute of an
exercise, and our goal is to
get as many reps of that
exercise as we can.
So what we're going to do is
we're going to do a little side
punching, so you can do this
three different ways.
We got the seated version, we
got Marcela
with the baseline,
and you can do it with me.
So what I'll be doing is a side
step
with a punch.
Side step, punch, punch.
So you're punching to the left
and the right.
You can pick which punch you
want to do.
You can do the jab, you can do
the hook, or the upper cut.
So you're just turning your
body to the side, throwing two
punches, same thing on the
other side.
All right, so each side that
you do, that's going to count
as one.
So in 10 seconds, we're going
to get started and try to get
in as many as we can.
So everybody get into your
stance, get that bounce going.
Let's get ready.
And here we go.
Side punches
in 3,
2,
1,
let's do it.
Nice shot, Marcela.
Good work, Avery.
Awesome job, everybody, keep it
going.
30 seconds, almost there.
20, keep it going, everybody.
Let's try to push a little bit
harder.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome job, everybody.
Good work, Marcela and Avery.
All right, on that note, let's
go take a break, so pull up
those chairs.
We're going to get about a
minute of resting before we
pick it back up for round
number two.
Way to go, everybody.
Awesome job.
All right, that was fun.
Worked our way through all
three of our punches.
Got a little cardio exercise in
there.
So next step, we're going to
work on some defensive moves
and bring those together to go
along with the punches.
Avery and Marcela, do you two
have a favorite punch of the
three?
I like the jab punch.
Jab punch, okay.
Marcela, which one do you like?
I like it all.
All of them?
Okay, you just like to throw
punches?
Yes.
How about you?
I like the upper cut, I like
the power punch.
Jab is fun, hook is good, but
the upper cut, just bring all
your energy together, and one
boom, that's it, done.
The jab punch is kind of like a
surprising punch, though, right?
So you can snap it real quick,
catch them.
And you don't have to use too
much energy either.
Yeah.
All right, everybody, if you've
got a favorite punch out there,
let us know in the chat.
All right, here we go.
So let's get back into it.
We're going to do round number
two now, and as I said, we're
going to add in some defense to
go along with the moves that we
already worked on.
So let's get to it.
First things first, we're going
to get into our boxing stance,
get those hands up, get that
bounce going.
All right, our first defensive
move, we're going to start off
with the shoulder roll.
So for the shoulder roll, we're
just leaning side to side,
rolling those shoulders left to
right.
Just imagine there's a punch
coming towards your face and
you've got to avoid that punch,
so roll your shoulders as quick
as you can so you don't get hit.
Let's go.
There's Avery doing a great job
with the quick side to side
movement, avoiding those punches.
Good work, everybody.
So we practiced left to right.
Let's do the same thing right
to left.
Awesome, Marcela.
Way to add in the footwork.
All right, everybody, we're
going to keep those shoulder
rolls going, but we're going to
add two jabs and then shoulder
rolls.
So we're going left, right jab,
following it up with the
shoulder rolls.
Good work, everybody.
Jab, jab, shoulder roll.
As Avery mentioned earlier,
after you finish your
combination, make sure you reset.
Get those hands back up.
Cover your face and your body.
Stay protected.
Awesome work, Avery.
Good job, Marcela.
All right, we're going to take
it a step further, everybody.
We're going to add in another
punch.
So we're still keeping our jab,
jab, shoulder roll, but we're
going to add in two hooks at
the end.
So jab, jab, shoulder roll,
shoulder roll, hook, hook.
Let's go.
Awesome work, Marcela.
Nice job with those.
Quick punches.
Quick shoulder rolls.
Awesome, everybody.
We got 10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Way to go, everybody.
Good job.
All right, Avery's
going to show us our next move.
All right, Kristian, our next
defensive move that we're going
to practice here today is going
to be the duck.
All right?
So if you're doing it seated
like myself, it's sort of like a
seated crunch.
So I'm just going to duck like
this.
My hands are still going to be
up.
My head is going to be up so I
can see.
I'm going to duck like this.
Okay, let's just practice.
You can check out Marcela and
Kristian if you're standing to
follow along with them.
Okay?
Great job, Marcela.
Remember, when you're ducking,
you still want to keep your
guard up.
Sometimes when you duck, that's
when you get caught with that
uppercut, Kristian.
Oh, yeah.
Hands up, everybody.
Great job.
All right, let's rock this out
for about another 20 seconds,
and then we're going to add
some punches.
Great work, everyone.
Keep it up.
All right.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
All right, we're still going to
keep our guards up.
We're still practicing our duck.
Now, this time around, we're
going to duck, and then we're
going to throw a right hook and
a left hook.
Okay, so we're going to duck,
right, left.
Guard's up, duck, right, left.
Great job transitioning,
everyone.
Good work, Kristian.
Excellent.
Great job, Marcela.
All right, 20 seconds.
All right, let's finish it out
strong, everyone.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
All right, we're going to keep
that same process going, but
this time we're going to
duck, hook, hook, duck again,
right uppercut, left uppercut.
Okay, so that's going to be a
duck,
hook, hook, another duck,
uppercut, upper cut.
Okay?
Duck, hook, hook, duck again,
uppercut, uppercut.
Great.
Just like that.
30 seconds.
Let's knock it out.
Literally.
Great work, Kristian.
Great job, Marcela.
All right, 15 seconds.
All right.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Great work, everyone.
Great work.
All right, Marcela, what do you
have for us next?
All right, our next defense
move is going to be the block.
So for this one, try to bring
those elbows together right in
front of our face to protect.
So we're going to start first
with our blocks.
Side to side blocks.
Again.
Just like that.
Very good.
Good job, Kristian.
Nice, Avery.
We're going to keep going with
this block, and we're going to
add some punches to the block.
Let's do that for another 10
seconds,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Good job, everyone, keep moving.
Time for our uppercuts.
So we're going to do a block,
uppercut, uppercut.
Block, uppercut, uppercut.
Nice.
Excellent.
Block,
and uppercuts.
Looking good, Avery.
Good job.
Nice, Kristian.
Good job, Marcela.
Get ready to add another punch.
So we're going to do
block, uppercut, uppercut,
block, jab, jab.
Block, uppercut, uppercut,
There we go.
A lot to think in here.
Nice work.
Good job, Kristian.
Nice, keep it up, keep it up,
almost there.
10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
SPIRIT.
Awesome.
All right.
Way to go, Marcela.
Way to go, Avery.
That was a real workout,
everybody.
Good job.
Let's go get another quick sip
of water.
All right, congratulations,
everybody.
We made it to the finish line,
and we did it with style.
You all did an amazing job
today.
So what we're going to do next,
we're going to finish it off
with some cool down stretches
so we can relax all those
muscles that we fired up today.
Our first stretch, we're going
to start off with the side bend.
We're going to get our core.
We did a lot of twisting and
turning.
We're going to
help those muscles relax by
bringing one arm up and over
and leaning to the opposite side.
We'll hold it for 10 seconds
and then switch.
3,
2,
and switch it up.
Same thing on the other side.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Good job.
Now we're going to take both
hands and we're going to reach
them down towards the floor,
and we're going to hold it.
If you're standing up, try to
keep those legs nice and
straight.
Reach down towards the floor.
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Good job.
Last one, everybody.
We're going to reach in the
opposite direction now, hands
up above our head.
Get those shoulders and arms
stretched out.
If you want to get your lower
back in the mix, you could push
your hips forward and lean back.
And we'll hold it for 10,
9,
GREAT!
7,
6,
5----------
4,
3,
2,
and SPIRIT.
Awesome job today, everybody.
Great work, Avery.
Good job, Marcela.
Awesome work, Kristian and
Avery.
And all of you, great job.
Great job, everyone.
Great work, Marcella.
Great work, Kristian, awesome
class, love the energy.
Lots of fun as always,
everybody, thank you all again
for being a part of this thing
with us.
We appreciate you, and we look
forward to seeing you next time.
So everybody take care and we
will catch up with you soon.